Kannika Henderson

QA & Software Engineer

Address: 1396 34th Ave,

San Francisco, CA

E-mail: Kanni-h@outlook.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.co

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kannika-henderson-

79b490145/

Summary

My over 10 years with experience in technology and collaboration skill. Interested in acquiring new technical knowledge and fast paced work environment, Professional under pressure, Ability to investigate issues in advance.

Key skills

Microsoft Office, Java, Jasper Reports, , HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL Server, Oracle, UNIX/LINUX, Agile methodology, MVC 2.0, CI system, Cucumber, Swagger, Json, Postman, SVN, Git, Rest API, Nunit Framework, Jira

Experience

Amazon Prime Now.(Part-time)

April 2019 – Present

Job Title: FC Associate I

- Selecting good quality items and packaging them under the expected time before delivery.
- Communicating with Whole Food team member for item not found.
- Rescue team member to make them success in time performance.

Agoda.com(Full-time)

May 2016 – October 2017

Job Title: Senior QA Engineer

- Review requirements with scrum team and design test case for content API platform.
- Created feature file for functional test to support CI system.
- Implemented A/B automated test and regression test with C#.
- Integration test to ensure content API result works properly on the frontend.
- Investigate issues and review bug description.
- Successfully complete a series of sprint goals.
- Communicate with different teams to clarifications of use cases.

Bangkok Payment Solutions Company Limited(Full-time)

October 2013 - April 2016

Job Title: Developer(Full-time)

Project: Rabbit/Carrot Reward (payment card for Bangkok mass transit system)

- Worked on stored procedure for calculating and generating data for reports.
- Developed system to generate reports to follow up kiosk performance.
- Provide and test SIT/UAT document for new version of full Touch Screen kiosk.
- Performance tuning data for Kiosk Management System on SQL server.

Project: Bangkok Mass Rapid Transit-Purple Line

- Created OST patch xml file and update database structure (Oracle database).
- Coordinate with staff in Australia office to ensure no data conflicts.
- Performance tuning data on Oracle database.

Bangkok OTP (one card to support multiple forms of transportation in Bangkok)

- Developed application on module Card Inventory Management with Java and Oracle database.
- Worked on UNIX/LINUX to generate data to test application.
- Created JIRA issued for update on agile process.

Outsourcing contracts

November 2012 – September 2013

Job Title: Software Engineer

Biz-CIS (Broker insurance company)

- Worked on stored procedures for updated data structure and data tuning.
- Transfer/Update data for insurance company on customer site.
- Developed and test insurance web application by VB.NET technology.

Ring Zero (Onsite Krungthai-AXA Life Insurance Project)

- Worked on stored procedures for updated data structure and tuning by SQL server and prepare data after converting spool file to database for populating data to template.
- Developed application for adjusting data from central Database to local project database.

Optimus Soft (Onsite at Thai Military Bank for National Credit Bureau Project)

- Developed application for management system with MVC 2.0 .NET technology and Oracle Database and Unit testing.
- Debugging code for sending auto email for incomplete data from validation control.

Neon InfoTech South East Asia(Full-time) Job Title: Application Software Engineer

May 2012 – October 2012

- Developed internal System & management database for marketing department by C#.NET and SQL server database.
- Developed Auto Email Expiration date for marketing control.
- Provided and support Smart Plan Software for oil & gas companies.
- Investigate system problems and contact with head office to fixed issues.

Sony Device Technology (Thailand) Co., Ltd. (Full-time)

September 2007 – April 2012

Job Title: Engineer2

- Full life cycle software engineer to support manufacturing production department.
- Developed and implement web database to support manufacturing production with VB.NET.
- Developed dynamic system chart to report management team with Dundas chart tool.
- Prepare & manage database for user requirements (SQL coding on stored procedures).
- Create/testing unit test, functional test and UI test.

Education

Bachelor's Degree - Computer Engineering Rangsit University

2007 Thailand

Language

Thai, English